https://www.trade-show-advisor.com/privacy-policy.html

Trade Show Advisor
Menu
Home
FREE Price QuotesExhibit EstimatesMarketing HelpImprinted Giveaways
Plan for SuccessPlanning TipsTimeline & ChecklistsFind Trade ShowsTrade Show ShippingSupplier Directory
Booth StrategyExhibits & DisplaysBanner StandsDesign & GraphicsFixtures & LightingStaffing Strategies
PromotionsMarketing StrategyTrade Show IdeasPromotional ItemsBooth Entertainment
Reach OutContact UsFind Tradeshow Jobs
Privacy Policy and User Terms
At Trade-Show-Advisor.com, we are committed to protecting your
data and privacy. The following information outlines the types of personal
information we receive and collect when you use Trade-Show-Advisor.com, as well
as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make
an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Trade-Show-Advisor.com strives to maintain the highest standards
of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are
dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.About Our CookiesA cookie is a string of information that Trade-Show-Advisor.com
may store on your computer, which your browser provides to Trade-Show-Advisor.com
each time you return to the site. We may use cookies to help us identify and
track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.Google Analytics CookiesTrade-Show-Advisor.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use
of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and
generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of
cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information
with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's
privacy policy is available at https://policies.google.com/privacy.Trade-Show-Advisor.com uses information from Google Analytics to
track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No
personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the
information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create
reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site
and improve your usage of it. If you do not wish your data to be collected via
Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on at
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/Advertising CookiesWe may use third-party advertising companies through Google Adsense
to serve ads on our website. A listing of those companies is at https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/9012903.
These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many
times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these
companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information
for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that
information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad
networks by visiting this link: https://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables
it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the
Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google opt-out page
at https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated. More information about how
Google manages data in its ad products may be found at https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.For information about BuyerZone, the non-affiliated, third party provider of no-obligation trade show product and service quotes, visit https://www.buyerzone.com/about-us/privacy/ for the company's privacy policy.Search FeatureThe search box on this web site is powered by Google Inc. You
acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy?/ shall
apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the search box you consent to
Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.Affiliate Products and ServicesWe receive an affiliate commission for some of the products and
services sold on Trade-Show-Advisor.com. The affiliate services platform we use
is ShareASale. By clicking on a product or service link, you consent to that
platform's use of cookies.  ShareaSale’s privacy policy is at https://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf.Refusing CookiesYou can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies
automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this
action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult
the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or
to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse Trade-Show-Advisor.com's cookies, you
may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.Personally Identifiable InformationTrade-Show-Advisor.com may collect and use your personal
information for the following purposes: To run and operate our site.To display content on the site correctly.To improve customer service.To help us respond to your requests and support needs
more efficiently.
To personalize your user experience.To understand how our users as a group use the services
and resources provided on our site.To improve our site.To improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site
feature.
To send information to you that you agreed to receive
about topics we think will be of interest to you.
To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other
requests.Trade-Show-Advisor.com may collect personally identifiable
information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when
you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection
with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our
site.If you complete a form, we will ask for your name, email
address, and information relevant to the purpose of the form.If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and email
address. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your
submission, may personally identify you. If you request to be notified about
comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others
submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable
information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from
engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally
identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site.
We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only
and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat
spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.Non-personally Identifiable InformationWe may collect non-personally identifiable information about you
whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information
may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information
about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and
the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.Children's Privacy ProtectionThis website is directed to adults. It is not directed to
children under the age of 18. We operate our site in compliance with current
regulations. Anyone under the age of 18 must provide parental consent to use
this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable
information from anyone under 18 years of age.Release of InformationIf we sell Trade-Show-Advisor.com, the information we have
obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer
to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may
continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that
change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure
that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and non-personally
identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's
servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard,
Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.If you wish to review your information stored on the SiteSell
servers for Trade-Show-Advisor.com, visit SiteSell’s link at www.sitesell.com
or [link to come]. You can also edit, download or delete any of your
information from the servers by clicking on that link.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our
commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have
submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would
like to update that information or have it deleted from our records, click here
[link to come] or visit our Contact page.Updates and Effective DateTrade-Show-Advisor.com reserves the right to make changes in
this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices,
we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a
link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review
this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use
it.Site EarningsThis website is free anytime for use. Like other types of
media outlets, there are paid advertisers, affiliate program links, and other
revenue-generating programs. You may find these links or banners placed within
or along side the editorial content.If a site visitor clicks on an advertiser's link, banner or
other form of advertising or purchases a product,  the publisher of this
site may receive a commission or other form of payment. Trade-Show-Advisor.com
is not liable in any way and for any reason for any action of an advertiser, affiliate or supplier.This website also displays advertisements from Google and other
sources. We have no control over the content of these advertisements. Google
determines what ads appear on any given page, based on the content. When a
visitor to the site clicks on one of the Google ads, the site publisher
receives a commission payment from Google.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to Trade-Show-Advisor.com's privacy policy
as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies
and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy
policy and terms in its entirety.DisclaimerAll information on this website is for informational purposes
only. The publisher/owner of Trade-Show-Advisor.com is not liable in any way
and for any reason for your use of the information. Last updated: May 27, 2018
Trade Show Advisor HOME
›
Privacy Policy and User Terms
HomeFREE Price QuotesExhibit EstimatesMarketing HelpImprinted GiveawaysPlan for SuccessPlanning TipsTimeline & ChecklistsFind Trade ShowsTrade Show ShippingSupplier DirectoryBooth StrategyExhibits & DisplaysBanner StandsDesign & GraphicsFixtures & LightingStaffing StrategiesPromotionsMarketing StrategyTrade Show IdeasPromotional ItemsBooth EntertainmentReach OutContact UsFind Tradeshow Jobs
[?]Subscribe To This Site
SUPPLIER DIRECTORY
TRADE ASSOCIATIONS
SITE SEARCH
CONTACT | ADVERTISE
Share Success Tips
Do you have a great exhibiting tip that enhanced
your tradeshow results? Share it here! What works for you may help others. Click here >>
ADVERTISING INQUIRIES | CONTACT US | PRIVACY POLICY & USER TERMS
Copyright 2005-2020 Sowder Group LLC. Content and images on this site may not be reproduced.  Content is for information purposes only.  The publisher is not liable in any way for your use of site information. Also, the publisher is not liable in any way for products, services or information provided by suppliers, affiliates or advertisers on this site. Thank you for visiting Trade-Show-Advisor.com.
